ほらみんな夢中だ
いつか きっと…
“Now you see her Now you don’t”
“See her？” “No I don’t ”
艦隊率いるあいつはまさしく
生まれる前からエイリアン
一つ言葉をくれたら 一つ転がり出す
COSMOS vs ALIENの戦い
いつでもマーベラス
二つ笑ってくれたら 二つ転がり出す
もっとたくさん集めたい
もっとたくさん見てみたい
こんな欲張りな私にした責任を
貴方にとってもらおう…
ミクロとマクロの距離感大事
宇宙規模での勘違いだけどね
One tumbles out when you talk to me.
アダムとイブの再来ならば
猫もしゃくしもいっそこのままで
いんじゃない？
ほら もっとよく見て
ほら もっと欲張って
Two tumble out when you smile at me twice.
ほら そっと手を取って
ほら とっとと笑って
I want to collect more. I want to see more.
トークトークのBPMは
とうにジョークの域を超えて
山超えて 谷超えて
あいつのいる星に届く
ほらきっと霧中だ
キャプテン・クィーンにSOS
ミサイル迎撃準備よし
弾道操るあいつはいかにも
生まれる前からエイリアン
いままさに宇宙は SPACE
いわゆるひとつのSWEET
甘い甘い宇宙のTASTE
Someday, you'll have to take responsibility
for making me so greedy.
魔法をひとふり あの子と二人きり
砂糖をひとふり あの子はいただき
The gallant all have an ambition or two
buried deep within their hearts.
漢たるもの 一つや二つ野望ってやつを
胸に秘めていて欲しいのよ…
Man or woman, all that matters
is your chivalrous spirit.
それは男女関係なく 漢気の話だ
I want you all to be chivalrous people.
諸君には 漢気ある
生き物であって欲しい
-そう思った俺が 昨日思いついた企画が これだ！
-うんうん ん？
I spent all day yesterday thinking about that,
King Game
and came up with this!
The King Game!
その名も“王様ゲ～～ム”！
King Game
え？ 王様ゲームって… くじ引いて
王様決めて 命令するってやつですか？
The King Game?
You mean that thing where you draw lots
and the winner can issue a decree?
何言ってんだお前…
What nonsense is that? There's only one
way to reach the throne in this game.
王座に座る方法はただ一つ！ 血みどろの
戦いに勝ち抜いた者だけだろーが！
You have to come out victorious in bloody battle!
What king in which period
are you getting that from?
何時代の王様の話なんでしょうね…
Chapter 183: "King Game"
You wanna be king?!
King Game
王様になりたいかー！？
Yeah!
You don't care about the consequences, right?!
罰ゲームは怖くないかー！
Right!
The Arakawa riverbank is about to play
host to a tournament of kings.
荒川河川敷で 王様ゲームという名の
最強決定戦が行われることになった
Come on. I'm not about to let you drag me
around according to your whims, Chief.
まったく… 村長の思いつきに
いちいち付き合ってられませんよ！
Count me out.
俺は参加しませんからね！
King Game
じゃ 失礼します
Now if you'll excuse me...
Don't you want to be king?
王様になりたくねーのか？
王様は一つだけ命令ができるんだぞ
The king can give one order. Any order.
It can be anything as long as the residents
of the riverbank can do it.
King Game
河川敷住人全員の力で
叶えられる事なら どんなものでもな
King Ga-
Really?! I'm in!
マジで！？ やる！ 俺出る!!
King Ga-
わ 私も出るわ！
Me, too!
King Ga-
Okay, okay.
A-Anything?
King Ga-
な… なんでもって…
So I could even tell these oafs I've spent
so long trying to teach common sense to,
俺が橋の下の学校で
常識と共に叩き込もうとしている
"Everyone except Nino has to speak
to me with utmost respect!"
“ニノさん以外全員が
俺に敬語” でもか！？
Hi, Mr. Rec. This suit sure does
get hot during the summer.
リクさ～ん 夏場はやっぱ
着ぐるみ暑いっすよ～
Hello, Mr. Rec. My, you look so nice today!
リクさんは今日もカッコイイですね～
You belong at the very top
of the food chain, Mr. Rec.
リクさんは生態ピラミッドの
一番上に行けますわ
Hey, Rec! If you're not in, get the hell outta here!
おいリク！ 出ねぇなら
とっとと帰れよな！
Even if you're just a pathetic worm, not having
you around will make my chances even better!
-テメーみてーなもやしでもいない方が有利… うっ！？
-フッ
Who are you calling pathetic?
誰がもやしだって？
I'm the omnipotent genius here!
この万能の才人 空手黒帯の
俺様の事じゃないだろうな！？
You wanna talk to this black
belt in karate like that?!
Y-You mean a white belt you haven't
washed in days, I bet...
な！？ ど どうせ
汚れきった白帯の事だろ！？
アッ ハッハッハーッ 言ってろ
ヘナチョコロッカー！
Say what you want, rock star wannabe!
Never mind that I got it when
I was in grade school...
ま 小学校の頃とったやつだけどな
If I knew you had a background in martial
arts, I would have actually seeded you.
King Game
なんだリク 武道経験あるって知ってたら
シード席用意したんだぜ
えっ 予選からあるんですか？
So there's a preliminary round?
King Game
Yeah.
おうっ
I don't mind. I seriously doubt I would lose
to something like this thing over here.
まあ いいですけどね
こんなのに負ける気がしませんから
て てんめー！
Asshole!
King Game
If you're participating,
come take a sheet of paper.
King Game
ほいじゃっ 参加者はこの紙一枚
持ってってくんなー！
King Game
I need you to decide your royal
decree before we begin.
一応先に 王様の命令を
決めといてもらうからな
Okay!
は～い！
先にですか？
We're doing it in advance?
うぉぉ… ひ 一つだけかぁ～
すげー迷うぜー！
Just one, huh? Man, I can't choose!
Same here! What should I do?
わ 私も…！ ん どうしようかなあ！
-ふ～ん… 命令っていうか願いだもんな…
-え～ どうしよう…
They seem to be thinking of it more
like a wish than an order.
They all look like they're having fun with it.
-みんなずいぶん… 楽しそうに…
-ふふっ 私の願いは決まっている
They almost look like joyful little kids.
-子供みたいな顔で書くんだな
-アハハハハ…
I imagine they're all pure-hearted wishes, too.
きっとそれだけ純粋な願いを…
Those two must be prevented from
taking the throne at all costs!
あの二人にだけは 王座を渡しては
いけないと思います！
Chapter 184: "Prelims Begin"
We will now begin the King Game preliminary
round, "Floating Battle Royale."
では 今から王様ゲーム予選
“水上バトルロイヤル”を開始する
The rules are simple. Whoever's left standing
on the raft will proceed to the finalist match.
ルールは簡単 最後までイカダに
乗っていられた者が 本戦出場だ
Okay... in the name of your ambition...
では 己の野望のために… ファイッ！
Fight!
A battle royale...
バトルロイヤルか…
こういう時は孤立したら不利だな
Anyone left by themselves will be
at a huge disadvantage here...
Hey, Rec.
よう リク
You wanna team up? You know, just for
now. To get rid of a few of the others.
今だけタッグを組んで
敵を減らしとかねぇか？
おー いいね星君 仲良くやろうか
Sounds good, Hoshi. Let's do this.
最後の二人になるまでの
束の間の友情だな
A temporary truce until we're
the last ones left standing!
Grownups always play dirty!
おっ 大人って汚いよ～
Aren't you two in the same boat?
何だよ お前らだって同じだろ
結局優勝は一人なんだぞ
Only one of us can win, you know.
We're different!
僕たちは違うもん
Yeah!
We don't have to say it out loud to know.
お互い言わなくたって分かってるんだ
We'll always wish for the same thing.
僕達は同じ願い事で
つながってるって… そう
We want to eat an oil drum full of...
-ドラム缶いっぱいのプリンを食べるっていうね！
-ドラム缶いっぱいのゼリーを食べるっていうね！
Jelly!
Flan!
-く…っ！ このっ 落ち…
-うっ… 落ち…
Get... off!
-ろーっ！
-お前が落…
Their brotherly bond fell apart like jelly.
兄弟の絆も ゼラチンに崩れたか
Okay, so... that's two down.
とにかく 二人減ったが…
You wanna take care of that
guy while we're still a team?
なぁ タッグを組んでるうちに
あの人を何とかしないか？
Yeah. He looks like he'll be the most trouble.
一番面倒なあの人か…？
Step off the white line, and my wife'll
turn into a White Cornish!
白線から出たら
妻が白色コーニッシュになる
A White Cornish chicken born to become nuggets!
食用鶏の白色コーニッシュに…！
I know we have to push him
off the raft to win, but...
けど どう何とかすんだよ…
イカダの外に出すっつったって…
I'm just a fraidy-cat punk rocker who doesn't
have the guts to push him off his white line!
あの人を白線外に押し出す勇気
俺みたいなヘナチョコロッカーにはないよ～
I wanna see your black-belt fortitude handle it!
君の黒帯の力が見たいなぁ！
What do you mean?
何言ってるんですかぁ
ロッカーの魂を見せて下さいよォ～！
Show me your soul as a true rock star!
でえぇーいっ！
Just do it!
いいから行けっつってんだよ
大人しく！
なっ お前が行けばいいだろ？
何で俺が！
You do it! Why should I?!
Hey.
おい
ムッ やるかい！？ 悪いが負けないよ！
妻を白色コーニッシュには…
You wanna go?! I'm not gonna lose to you! I
won't let anyone turn my wife into a White Corn—
You got a problem with birds?!
鳥類の何が不満だ コラァ！
H-Hey, Billy! If you knock him
off that white line of his...
ちょ… ビリーさん その人は
白線の外に出しちゃ…
Stop your squawking.
What are you, tiny little chicks?!
ピーチクパーチクさえずるんじゃねぇ
小鳥か てめぇらは！？
い いくらタイハクオウムだからって
非人道的すぎる…！
Even if you're really a cockatoo,
this is just inhuman!
どうする？ このままじゃシロが…
What do we do?! Whitey's gonna...
Hmph. My feathers always seem to
start falling out this time of year.
チッ 羽のよく抜ける季節だぜ…
He's still on the white line!
あれだったら白線から出てねぇ！
What's his deal?! I feel like I can't beat him
for a totally different reason than Whitey!
な 何だあの人は！？ シロと
違う意味で勝てる気がしねぇぞ！
くそっ かっこよすぎる！
一体どうしたら…！
He's just too cool! We can't contend with that!
Billy, you're so wonderful.
ああビリー なんて素敵なの
My lovebird...
マイ・ラブバード
い 今だわ… 後ろから押すなんて
卑怯かもだけど…
Now's my chance. It might be cheap
of me to push her from behind...
But I have my ambition!
私にも野望があるんだからーっ！
キャッ あ… え… あ…
ああーーっ！
フンッ
ビ ビリー… だめじゃない
あなたも場外に…
Billy, no! Now you're out of bounds, too...
Stop talking. I hate the screams of my woman
more than anything in the world.
-耳障りなんだよ 自分の女の悲鳴ってのが一番な
-あ…っ！
Don't you do anything that dangerous ever again!
二度と危険な事すんじゃねぇぞ！
Big Bro!
アニキィ～～！
Chapter 185: "Gateway to the Greatest"
Three contestants left!
残りはあと三人 予選を
通過するのは 一体誰なのか！？
Who will make it through this initial round?
It's about time I broke up my
little alliance with him.
そろそろ こいつとのタッグも
解消だな…
Maybe I should get rid of P-ko before
taking out that idiot Hoshi.
星のバカの前に
一応Ｐ子を倒しておくか…
I'll just talk to her nice and easy to get
her guard down while I inch closer...
まずは 警戒させないように
話しかけながら近づいて…
You really helped us out there, P-ko. We had
no idea how we were gonna handle Billy.
いや～ でも助かったよＰ子！
ビリーさんに勝てる気がしなくて
困ってたけど
Thanks to how you won against Jacqueline—
Ｐ子がジャクリーンに
勝ってくれたおかげで…
I didn't win.
勝ってなんかないわよ
う… Ｐ子？
P-ko?
When she was in dire need, the love
of her life came to her rescue.
ピンチの時に好きな男性が
助けてくれるジャクリーンと
I wanted to get the attention of my love
by pushing someone else into the river.
好きな人を振り向かせるために
人を川に突き落とそうとした私…
P—
Ｐ…
I may have won the battle,
but I completely lost as a woman!
戦いに勝って女として完全に
負けたわぁぁぁー！
ひっ どうせこんな私は
一生片想いで終わりよぉ～！
This love I feel will probably never go
anywhere for the rest of my life!
Uh, P-ko?
-うわあああ～ん
-ちょっ Ｐ子！？
What's wrong?!
-なになに どうしちゃったの！？
-うえええ～ん
I think she's starting to despair
over her love for the Chief.
何か村長との恋路に急に
絶望しちゃったみたいで…
何で！？
Why?
うわあああ～ん！
We need to get her to stop crying.
ま まあ 泣きやませよーぜ
It'd leave a real sour taste in my mouth if we
pushed her off now while she was still crying.
どーせ落とすにしたって泣いてるところ
落としたら サイテーもいいとこだからな…
Yeah...
だよな…
Uh, P-ko.
あー… あの Ｐ子？
一生片想いなんて事はないと思うよ
I don't think it'll be an unrequited love forever.
うっ うっ 何よ 適当な事言って
Whatever! You're just saying that.
You know, whenever we see the two of
you together, you look really close.
いや でもはたから見てても
本当仲いいじゃない
I'm just saying that, of course.
もちろん適当だが
Yeah! You two make a great couple!
そうそう！ 二人並んでると
絵になってんぜ～
Since red and green go together.
赤と緑で
Really?
Yeah, really. I always see the Chief
wandering around looking for you.
ホントホント 村長が
Ｐ子捜してんのもよく見るし
キュウリ欲しさに
Looking for cucumbers.
なんかハラヘッタなー
I'm so hungry.
Yeah. He always has this kind
gaze when he looks at you.
そうそう！ Ｐ子を見る目も
心なしか優しいよな
Especially after he gets those cucumbers.
特にキュウリをもらった後は
やっぱコレコレ！
I love 'em!
Yeah, we're totally serious!
いや～ もう ホントさ～
Maybe he fell for you and didn't even know!
実はもう両想いとか？
Oh, that's enough. Stop it, you two!
やっ やだも～ やめてよ二人とも！
うおっ とっとっとっととと…
But I suppose we have been meeting
each other's gaze a lot lately.
-ととと… ていっていっ… うおーっ！
-確かに最近村長とよく目が合うし
And he does sit next to me
whenever we all eat together.
みんなでご飯食べる時横に座ってきて
くれたりとか もうヤダァ～！
How embarrassing!
予選突破 Ｐ～～子！
P-ko wins the preliminary match!
Huh? Where'd everyone go?
何？ あれっ？ え… リク達は？
Congratulations, P-ko.
おめでとう Ｐ子
え？ 何… もしかして私勝ったの！？
Huh? What happened? Did... did I win?!
Yeah! You're in the finals now!
ああ 本戦出場だ
Your love for the Chief brought you this victory.
村長への想いの強さの勝利だな
Y-Yeah!
All right, next up we have a
no-holds-barred battle royale!
さあ いよいよ次は… ルール無用の
ガチンコバトルステージだ！
うわあああ～っ 流れが速い～！
The current's too strong!
At that moment, P-ko heard the lid covering
the cauldron of hell creak open...
確かにその時Ｐ子は 地獄の
釜の蓋が開く音を聞いたという！
The Death Omen Star of Arakawa, Stella!
The Emerald God of War, Chief!
The Reverse-blade Stylist, Last Samurai!
The Queen of Disaster, P-ko!
The final battle in the Arakawa
King Game is about to begin!
荒川王様ゲーム王座をめぐる本戦が
今 幕を開けようとしていた！
A balloon battle?
風船バトル！？
Yup.
So you lose if your balloon pops?
Sounds like a pretty tame battle.
風船割られたら負けって
随分かわいいバトルなのね
And now you're acting like you've
been the referee the entire time.
そしてリクは ナチュラルに審判なのね
You're also done if you go out of bounds.
それと 場外も負けだね
あ そっかぁ よかった～
Oh, really? That's a relief.
Considering the other contestants, I was thinking
about forfeiting. But I might just have a chance!
あまりのメンバーに棄権も考えたけど
これなら私でも勝ち目が
あるかもしれないわ！
あ ああ それと…
Oh, there's one other rule to make
this a peaceful, fair match.
平和かつ紳士的な戦いにするために
規制が一つ…
Weapons are—
凶器は…
うん うん そりゃぁね…
Oh, yeah, of course.
limited to one per person.
一人一つまで…
ありなのぉーっ！？
So they're allowed?!
Chapter 186: "Bloodsport"
Somebody help!
だ だ 誰かぁ～～っ！
Calm down, P-ko! You can still forfeit
right now if you want to!
落ち着けＰ子！ 今なら
棄権できるんだから安心して
Somebody go get my hoe from the field!
誰か 私の畑からクワ持ってきて！
二つあるけど大きい方のね！
There's two! Bring me the bigger one!
Okay!
は～い
おっきい方ね！
The big one, right?
We're on our way!
取ってきま～す！
I'm really scared. I hope
everything turns out okay...
あ～ 怖いわ… 大丈夫かしら…
Oh, but maybe I should use the
smaller one for better mobility.
あっ 小さい方が小回りがきくかしら？
I'm worried that you picked a hoe as
your weapon without hesitating!
俺は迷わずクワを選んだ
お前が怖いよ…
Let me make this clear, Stella.
I won't be going easy on you.
ステラよ 言っておくが
一切手加減せんからな
That's my line. Because my ambition is...
それはこっちの台詞じゃけん…
わしの野望…
to make Maria my mother! And I'll fight
to the death to make it happen!
“マリアにお母さんになってもらう”ために
全力で戦うからの！
Actually, I've been thinking about entrusting
the future to the next generation.
いや… 実は私もそろそろ若い者に
未来を託そうかと思っていたところでな
So I've decided to assist you
with everything I've got!
やはり私は 全力でお前に
力を貸す事にしよう！
ほんとけー！？
Really?!
Hey, that clergyman just lied to a little girl.
おい 今嘘ついたぞ あの聖職者！
Here's your hoe, P-ko.
はい Ｐ子ちゃん クワだよぉ～
Thanks!
ありがと～ フンッ！
Well, now that everyone is ready... let's begin!
じゃあ まあ準備も整ったみたい
なので… 試合開始～！
The balance of power is gonna get really
messed up if Sister and Stella team up.
しかし… シスターとステラが手を組んだら
パワーバランスが崩れすぎてしまうんじゃ…
Stella, assume Formation A!
ステラ フォーメーションＡだ！
フッ 懐かしいのぅ…
That takes me back...
I remember those days on the
battlefield, back in England.
イギリスでの戦いの日々を思い出すわ…
Yes. Back then we were feared as
the Tower of Eastern Europe.
そうだ あの時代… “東ヨーロッパの
巨塔”と恐れられた…
これが
This is...
Formation A!
フォーメーションＡよォォ！
Damn! Sister's skirt is protecting
Stella's balloon...
なんてこった…！
シスターのスカートで
ステラの風船は守られ…
While Sister's balloon is too
high for anyone to reach!
シスター殿の風船は
高すぎて届かない！
That's right! With Nino's jumping
ability, she just might-
いや そうか！ ニノのジャンプ力を
持ってすれば あるいは…！
スキだらけだぞ ニノ！
You're wide open, Nino!
She failed!
ダメだったでござったか！
い いや よく見ろ！ 今のはダミーの
鼻ちょうちん… 風船は割れてない！
No! Look!
She used her snot bubble as a decoy!
Her balloon is still intact!
Sister, no! You only get one weapon per person!
シスターいけんぞ！？
武器は一人一個まで…
Nino fell victim to her instincts,
taking her out of bounds!
ニノさん 本能にあらがえず退場～～！
くっ… おやつは凶器には含まれない！
Snacks don't count as weapons!
考えたな…！
Smart move...
ぬーん！
I could beat you as is, but I need to
save my strength for the very end.
戦って勝てない事ないけど…
決勝まで力を温存しておかないとね
Stella!
ステラちゃ～ん
You shouldn't get so big!
I can see right up your skirt!
ダメよ～ そんなに大きくなっちゃ～
スカートの中 丸見えよ～
いけーん！
レディーのわしとした事がー！
That's unbecoming as a lady!
はしたなぃっ！
Stella is eliminated!
ステラ脱落ー！
There, there. Don't cry.
はいはい 泣かない
Stella, I'll take over your ambition!
ステラよ お前の志は私が必ず…！
Then I'd better make sure I don't lose.
あ～ら じゃ絶対に負けられないわね
ステラちゃんのお母さん代わりは
構わないけど
I don't mind becoming Stella's mother.
But I don't want some pervert
father tagging along with her!
もれなく変態お父さんが
ついてくるのは ごめんなのよね
You don't understand!
That was never my intention!
誤解だマリア！ 私にはそんな下心はっ
１％の信仰心と99％の下心で
できてるくせに
Yeah, right! You're made of one percent faith
and ninety-nine percent bad intentions!
よく言うわよ
Excellent. The two most likely winners
are now locked in battle.
よし 優勝候補の二人の
手がふさがっているうちに
I shall take this opportunity
to do a little spirit hunting.
拙者は 妖怪退治といくでござるよ
おおっと！ ラストサムライが
刀を抜いた！
Last Samurai has drawn his katana!
The Chief is unarmed! He's in real trouble here!
しかし村長は武器を持ってない…
これは不利！
フッ 刃物なんかより強力な
“妖術”を見せてやるよ…
I'll show you my spirit magic,
far more powerful than any sword.
なっ！？ 髪が逆立って…
His hair is standing on end? No!
いや！ 皿だ！ 皿が高速回転を…
これはすごい！
His head-plate is spinning! Simply incredible!
これはすごい服だ～！
What an amazing suit!
I told you, magic!
妖術だっつってんだろ
ムッ スキありーっ！
You're mine!
Last Samurai is eliminated!
ラストサムライ脱落ー！
なっ！？ くっ… しかし手ごたえは
拙者にもあったでござる…！
But I know for a fact I cut something!
Why did I not hear his balloon pop?
それなのになぜ… 風船の割れる音が…
フッ 俺の見事すぎる黒髪に
目がくらんだか…？
Did my raven locks, too beautiful for
their own good, cloud your vision?
あ… ああああ…あ！
I relied on your instincts as a hair stylist.
貴様の美容師としてのサガまで
計算し尽した… 俺の勝ちDEATH！
And so, I claim victory...
How could you tell you had that visual-kei
look even without a mirror?
鏡見てないのに よく自分がビジュアル系に
カットされたってわかりますね…
Chapter 187 "Fateful Bout"
キャアアア～～ッ
村長 カ カ… カッコイイ～！
Chief! You're so b-beautiful!
Really? Maybe take another look.
そうか？ よく見てみ？
P-ko. Our time to battle has come.
おぅＰ子 次は俺達が戦う番だな
I'm serious about this. You should be, too.
本気でいくから 本気でこいよ
We both have our own ambitions!
お互いの野望のためにな…！
Th-That's right. My ambition
is to get the Chief to like me!
そ そうよ 私の野望… 村長に
好きになって貰う事のため…！
えっ… でも それじゃあ
村長の野望は…！
Then what's the Chief's ambition?
I can't see. I better pull this back.
Am I ready to destroy the dreams of my love
just so I can force him to love me back?
私は 自分が愛する人に愛されるために…
愛する人の夢を奪おうっていうの！？
I...
I can't...
出来ない…！
P-ko!
Ｐ子！？
The Chief's happiness is more important
to me than my own ambitions.
私は 私の野望より… 村長の
幸せの方が大切だもの…！
P-ko, does that mean you—
ピ Ｐ子 それって…！
ま まさかＰ子のやつ…？
Is P-ko—
あ！ やっぱり！ どんなに村長が鈍くても
今のじゃ告白したようなもの…！
I knew it! The Chief may be totally blind, but
she basically just confessed her love to him!
I knew it. That's...
間違いない！ あれは…
The "No Guard" stance!
“両手だらり戦法”！
Did she really master that legendary art?!
伝説のアレをマスターしてしまったと
言うのか！？
フッ フフ… ごめんね村長…
もう分かっちゃったよね…
I'm sorry, Chief. I guess you know by now...
You know what I'm thinking. But I don't care.
私の考えてる事…
でもいいの 私目が覚めた
気分なのよ… へへ…
This was a big eye-opener for me.
へっ… 言われなくても分かってらぁ！
Believe me, I know how you feel!
Let's do this, P-ko!
行くぜ Ｐ子！
Ch-Chief?
そ 村長！？
You got it all wrong! Dodge, P-ko! The Chief
is looking at you like your name is Joe!
違うぞ！ 避けろＰ子！
村長は お前の中に
“ジョー”を見てるんだ！
Right here in public?! I'm not ready for this!
どうしよう こんな人前で…
で でででも 私…
Get away before you get hurt!
怪我する前に逃げろー！
You're mine!
よし もらったぁーっ！
And I...
私っ 村長のこと…！
CROSS COUNTERRRR!!!
クロスカウンターー!!
I love you, Chief...
好きよ… 村長…
Both fighters are down!
両者 気絶につき脱落ー！
The Chief was still green, even after burning up...
村長は燃え尽きても
緑色だったといいます
Chapter 188: "March to the Finals"
Well, crap. It looks like Sister and Maria have
earned their spots in the final showdown.
決勝進出はこれで シスターとマリアに
決定… してしまいましたー！
Did I hear you say "crap"?
What's that supposed to mean?
してしまいましたって ずいぶんな
言い草ねぇ うふふ…
ううっ… 問題はこの人が
優勝した場合だ…
There's gonna be big problems if she wins...
I just know she's gonna lay down an order
beyond anyone's wildest imagination!
絶対に想像を絶するような 恐ろしい
命令をしてくるに決まっている！
Sister! You're all we've got left.
シスター！ もうあなただけが
頼りですよ！
好きな人だからとかで遠慮しないで
思いっきり勝ちにいって下さいね！？
You can't afford to go easy on her just because
you like her. You have to fight and win!
Of course.
当然だ… 先の戦いでも
一撃もくらっていないからな…
I didn't take a single hit in the fight so far.
But before we begin...
だがその前に…
Is anyone here blood type A?
誰かこの中に… Ａ型の人はいるか…
O is fine, too!
Sister!
-シスター！
-Ｏ型でも…
You dodged every single physical attack,
but all the mental strikes landed clean!
肉体攻撃は全てかわしても…
精神攻撃は残らず
ヒットしてるじゃないですかー！
The final battle in the Arakawa
King Game has begun!
怒涛の展開を見せた
荒川王様ゲーム本戦！
Who will grasp their ambition and hold
the championship belt up high?
野望という名のチャンピオンベルトを掴むのは
果たして シスター マリアのどちらなのか！？
Sister or Maria?
緊張の決勝戦は 次回
「13BRIDGE×２」
Chapter 189: "Arakawa Open-Air Classroom, 4th Period"
Whitey's White Line Lesson
Okay, then. Let's begin class.
I'd like to begin by teaching you the names
of each part of the line marker.
旅の終わりに想うもの
Let's see...
Whitey's White Line Lesson
Oh?
求めるだけの日々は過ぎる
Nice! This is a very nice white line!
This is amazing! I had not anticipated this!
冬を待たずにはしゃいでる
I had no idea these little white
lines held such potential!
Whitey's White Line Lesson
Take a look at this free-flowing line!
赤いコートに包まれる君
It's like a beautiful swan taking flight!
さよなら迷宮days
Whitey's White Line Lesson
Ohh, did you see it? Did you see that curve?!
気づけばThank you days
Oh ～ good bye days
I see! Positioning the chalk tip at a slight
diagonal will make the inner side even smoother!
Speaking of inside and outside, you know
those train station announcements,
where the announcer is like,
"Please stand behind the white lines"?
I really think they should change it to say,
"Please stand on the white lines"!
旅の始まり想うもの
Just saying "behind" the white lines could mean
left or right! It's so confusing, don't you think?!
立ち止まらずに深呼吸する
White lines should never be confusing
in any way whatsoever!
ふたり明日を泳いでる
Furthermore, the white lines have
the White Deity that says...
魚みたいに並び揺れる
Recruit...
What, Nino? Why so formal all of a sudden?
Can you make me fall in love?
辛いNo thank youです
Sure. Leave it to me!
悲しいNo thank youです
Next time,
on 13 BRIDGE x2!
Oh no ～ good bye days
Ride the wave and escape the atmosphere!
Wait! I'm not
prepared for that!
Illustration: Arina Tanemura
ヘイッ それじゃあ授業を始めるよ～
まずは ラインマーカーの
部分名称について説明しようね
ええと…
おや？ むむむ… いいね！
実にいい白線だ！
うん これは凄いぞ！
いやはやこれは盲点だったね～！
まさか まだ白線にこんな
可能性があるとは…
ほら見てごらん この自由なライン！
まるで大空へ飛び立つ白鳥の如し！ だよ
おお～！ 見たかい 今のカーブ！
なるほど チョークの先端をやや斜めに
押さえ付けるようにして動かすと
より内側が滑らかに…
ああ 内側といえば思い出したんだがね
駅でアナウンスされる “白線の内側に
お入り下さい”ってアレ…
やっぱりね “白線の上にお乗り下さい”って
した方がいいと思うんだよ～
だってさ 白線の内側って白線の右？ 左？
どっちにいけばいいんだって思わないかい？
大体白線は そんな混乱を招くような
存在であっちゃいけないんだよ
そもそも白線には…
リクルート
何ですかニノさん 改まって
私に恋をさせてくれないか？
ええ 任せて下さい！
次回 「13 BRIDGE×２」
デンパに乗って大気圏突破だ！
待って！ そっちはまだ心の準備がっ！